(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
​Death needs a Rosary to be
He is the guide to ascending to heaven.
But you have to cut it before you can love it so it doesn't follow.
-death in the family follows.
Ate!
Leave me alone with SHIELD.
SHIELD.
Anti-Bacterial Soap.
It's over.
He probably thought someone would kill me.
newbie.
Don't you dare touch Ma.
Why do you still trust him?
He betrayed you?
And your friends?
I need to infect you.
You mean Mom.
Need to say something.
I need to tell you.
Help.
Then.
I'm still the supremo of this school.
I can choose who is under me.
my protection.
Mr. President, you must never forget the only
rule of your position.
That you must never get involved with anyone.
This is also what Lex started.
You must know, I am not in place
without one.
So if you see Buyas now, you know
You know what's next.
What?
Of course, you can cut it.
So of course, you'll get the blade away like that.
Just keep going.
That's great.
Try it.
This.
Ah, it seems too complicated.
Are you sure?
Come on, Zane.
You'll be fine.
You know, you're just experiencing this now.
Heaven Mom or Liver
Allison is the cook.
I am a foodie or a foodie.
You'll be fine, Zane.
Come on, try it.
Are you sure?
Everyone.
Say.
How?
Put the blade away.
Sandahang.
Okay?
That's it.
Of course, continuously.
How is that?
Is this difficult?
This?
Yes.
Oh!
Tears of joy?
Am I this happy now?
Tears of joy.
Oh?
Why are you laughing?
Tears of joy indeed.
That's really what Buyas is, isn't it?
It's like love.
Tears well up.
You are so corny!
How corny!
Who is in tears?
How again?
Keep it out of your hands.
Today!
Oh!
Come here!
I'll spank you Vanessa!
Go ahead!
Today!
Just wait!
Where are you going?
Today!
Oh!
You're just here.
Who are they?
P-P-G?
D-G-W?
I don't know.
I had a great time.
If you have nothing more to say, is that okay?
you leave?
What?
Do you know?
Who owns that cat?
That cat was owned by Lux, former Supreme
Student Government President Pati
Lux's girlfriend, who is
Samantha.
They also killed.
Just like Headmaster Valdez, who also happens to
be Lux's father.
He died.
All of them.
They killed everyone.
You want to know the truth, right?
What did he die of?
Just a few more minutes.
It's midnight.
Please.
Please, tell me the truth.
See you tomorrow at 1:00 PM.
I will tell you everything I know.
Don't do this, Supremo.
You will only harm yourself.
I know.
You know the rules, Supremo.
You should have just punished him.
Ms. Kat is right.
You'll lose your authority.
I can live without this position.
What does Mission really mean to you?
Supreme?
She's my secretary.
I need to protect her.
And that's understandable.
But you could lose your job.
We're just concerned, Supremo.
We don't want to harm you.
And I don't care.
He can't be lost.
I need her.
I understand, Supremo.
I guess it's best for now if we
just focus first on the foundation day.
And I don't care.
He can't be lost.
I need her.
Why am I smiling?
I think I've been infected by Celine.
Speaking of Celine.
Are you sure you really wanna know everything?
Remember the formula I was telling you about?
There's more to it than that.
Many people are interested in that formula.
Including Mr. Valdez, Violet, and
Francisco.
But Dr. Kizon.
Because he knows he will also trade three
That's it.
So he stopped the experiments.
The three rang.
So they did something crazy to get the
formula that led to murder.
Mr. Valdez, Violet, and Francisco killed the
headmaster to get the formula.
But that's not complete yet.
As the second highest Mr. Valdez, he
succeeded Dr. Kizon.
Together with Violet and Francisco, they continued
research on the missing formula.
And to the only person who knows the secret
ingredient to complete it.
Did I think Mr. Valdez was nice?
Why is he interested in the formula?
It will power?
No, it's not that.
Because he wants to bring his wife back to life.
Mr. Valdez has one child, Luxury.
Valdez, ang SSG president.
Everything was going well until something happened.
Three people also lost their way in hell.
to.
But what stands out in everyone's mind is
The name is Samantha.
Samantha was a big influence in the life of
Lux.
The once sluggish Supreme, suddenly revived and
he convinced Supremo.
He managed to get his father to give him a ride.
All of this.
Because they're just making it harder for themselves.
And it worked.
For a few days, it was still easy.
university the to.
Until Madam Violet noticed this and
Mr. Francisco.
And they tightened it even more to the point
that no one has been able to get out.
After the deaths of Mr. Valdez, Lux, Samantha,
Hell University has been closed again.
Where are you?
Take him back there.
Face us.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Again?
Why are we here?
What is that?
Did you see me? Who is that?
I don't know.
I don't know what his name is but
I always see him.
He's always following you too.
What are you saying?
They are always thorough.
Ha?
They?
Who are they?
I don't know!
I'm scared, I'm scared!
Zane, if anything bad happens to me, please,
Please tell Supreme Patawan.
What do you say, Celine?
I have to be sure!
Now I'm the one who's been dragging you along until now.
Celine, Celine!
Wait a minute, Celine!
Where are you going?
Celine!
Where am I?
You're here in the faculty dorm.
What happened?
I saw you in the forest.
The most expensive.
Celine?
I was with him earlier in the day.
But he disappeared.
Did you see the gap?
You are the only one there.
There are people inside the hut.
It's not just us.
Celine ran and then, suddenly, she
lost.
Celine!
I was trying to look for anyone.
I don't remember anymore.
Suddenly everything went dark.
Did you notice anything different about the wood?
Secret lab?
Did he mention anything about this?
No.
No lab.
Let's group and...
Where are you going?
Maybe my friends are worried.
It's not safe for you to go out there.
You can spend your time here.
Sorry po, sir.
If I hadn't found the hidden laboratory yet.
Don't worry about it.
You can't make this a secret lab if it's easy.
find, right?
Look at this.
Yeah.
What exactly are you planning to do with my hair?
Enough, trust me.
I'm giving you a new hairstyle.
Hmm.
Go ahead, think about it.
Wow!
You are great!
Of course!
Beautiful.
Oh, make-up for next, huh?
Leave it or we might be late for
our perfect ones.
Bia, have you seen my cap?
Cap?
Jerome is so careless, huh?
I just didn't put it down.
Wow!
Look who's talking.
You really thought he wasn't sloppy.
Hi, hi, hi.
Oh, this.
I saw it, scattered on the lips.
Don't let that go, okay?
Nice.
Thanks, Van.
Wow!
The morning.
Did you dream?
Don't ruin the trip.
You know the opponent is bored, right?
Don't just let it go by sight.
That's why you guys are arguing, huh?
If you really want it, make a move.
You know, Dave is right.
You remember, pre.
If you are the first blood, you have the
advantage.
Really?
What are you doing?
Ha?
Stop it.
You're right, huh.
Matt?
Are you okay?
Or do you need something?
You.
You're the only one I need, Zane.
Oh!
Hi!
You look beautiful, Zane.
I'm surprised to hear that, huh?
That's really good!
Right!
Oh, Zane.
Can we be together later?
Ah.
Okay.
Really?
Is that true?
Yes!
Okay.
Are you okay, baby?
Just wait, okay?
I just have a question.
Excuse me.
Have you seen Celine?
No.
That's a dead kid, right?
Maybe he's just drawing.
Okay.
Say, thanks.
Matt, you know, you're good at it.
Ah, but...
What is it, Cindy, babe?
Foundation Day.
Free Bloody Night later.
No weapons, no exceptions.
Why are you here?
Look, you have so many beautiful boots.
It's over, huh.
Here we are.
Okay.
We'll start with the bonfire first.
Then there are the fireworks.
I expect everything to be executed in the
right flow.
Got it?
Yes, Mr. Vice President.
But don't forget, tonight is Free Bloody Night,
but zero tolerance for weapons in the field.
Wait lang.
You know, we should have taken a picture.
Camera, camera, camera.
Say, say, say.
Thanks, Jerome.
Here, here.
Okay, one, two, three.
Say, cheese!
Cheese!
Yay!
I'm excited to develop this.
Hell can be peaceful.
You know, right?
Just don't let the gangs get into trouble.
This peacefulness is really amazing.
Speaking of the devils, they are here.
Right.
Matt?
Are you okay?
Why is your hand so dirty?
It's stressful.
Why is there suddenly such a commotion here?
Of course.
Nakatens.
That was close.
Attention to all candidates.
Go backstage.
OMG, Matt.
Are you ready?
Okay, that's it.
Very much.
Wish me luck?
Let's go, pre!
Why?
What's up?
It's just a surprise now.
What are you?
You are still hiding.
What is that?
Secret na.
Don't get too excited.
It's annoying.
What, come on?
My number, my number.
Let's go.
Okay, girls.
A little backward.
Then you, sister, go ahead.
There in the back.
Okay, backward.
Then, there you go.
Perfect.
Next time.
Okay.
Next, boys.
Just straight ahead.
Okay.
There you go.
Say.
Just straight ahead.
There you go.
You choose.
It's about to start.
Oh, right?
We really didn't make a mistake in choosing Matt.
to be a representative of our class.
And...
It's not his first time, right, Zane?
Good design.
Miyo is saying.
Ha?
Yes, indeed.
Together with you.
That's it.
Matt's kinda hot, right?
Ha?
What's hot?
Oh, wow.
He is still very spicy.
You really can't hide our excitement,
Design.
You saw me again.
Kasimta.
It's like your eyes have learned to
Matt, e.
What are you?
Yes, you're not thrilled.
Oh, wow.
That's great, that's why.
Hey, Zane is looking at you.
Say.
Of course, he's on stage.
Well, that face.
It's okay.
Candidates, we will start in a few minutes.
Okay?
Come back.
Hi!
Good luck, to.
You're welcome, sir.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Good luck, Matt.
Make our section proud!
Sure.
I won't let you go.
For you.
Don't you have a good luck kiss, Zane?
What is that?
Just one.
You don't know the rules in this competition?
What are the rules?
I organized the rules for this event.
We are not breaking any rules.
There's actually one.
If you are one of the participants, you are not
You can kiss or be kissed by anyone.
Especially with your friends.
Oh no, just a hug.
Not even a hug.